邪恶力量前情提要
Previously on Supernatural
萨姆
Sammy.
赶快带你弟弟离开屋子 快
Take your brother outside as fast as you can. Go!
爸爸已经踏上了捕猎之旅
Dad's on a hunting trip.
他好几天没回家了
And he hasn't been home in a few days.
这是爸爸的笔记
This is Dad's book.
我想他想让我们继续他的工作
I think he wants us to pick up where he left off.
救助他人 猎杀恶魔
You know, saving people, hunting things.
家族事业
The family business.
我得找到爸爸
I gotta find Dad.
这是现在我唯一想干的
It's the only thing I can think about.
《邪恶力量》
(希宾 明尼苏达州)
它通过大桥
It's coming across the bridge.
快点
Hurry!
啊 不 不
Ah! No! No!
我知道这是你的本职工作
l know you're just doing your job
但警察一个礼拜之前就来过这里了
But police have been here all week.
我不明白为什么还要再询问这些
I don't see why we have to go through this again.
这事复述了多了 会让他自己也开始相信了
The more he tells the story, the more he believes it's true.
麦凯太太
Mrs. McKay...
我们知道你已经向地方当局反映过这事
we know you spoke with local authorities.
但看来这是应该属于是州警局的事
But this seems like a matter for the state police. So....
所以别担心那事听上去多不可思议 埃文
Don't worry how crazy it sounds, Evan.
你知道把你所看到的 告诉我们就可以了
You just tell us what you saw.
我看电视看到很晚…
I was up late watching TV...
然后我听见很奇怪的声音
when I heard this weird noise.
那声音象什么
What did it sound like?
就象怪物发出的声音
lt sounded like a monster.
告诉他们你在看什么节目
Tell the officers what you were watching on TV.
"哥斯拉对魔斯拉"
Godzilla vs. Mothra.
那部哥斯拉是我最喜欢的一部
That's my favorite Godzilla movie.
- 比之前的那部好看多了 - 百分之百的
- So much better than the original, huh? - Totally.
没错
Yeah.
好象是重新拍的
He likes the remake.
- 很恐怖的 - 这就是我
- Yuck. - That's what I
埃文 你有看见那个到底是什么东西吗
Evan, did you see what this thing was?
没有 但我看见它抓住了詹金先生
No. But I saw it grab Mr. Jenkins.
他被那东西推倒在车下
lt pulled him underneath the car.
然后怎么样
Then what?
他被那怪物拖走了
It took him away.
我有听见那怪物离开
I heard the monster leaving.
那声音真可怕
It made this really scary sound.
那声音象什么
What did it sound like, Evan?
就象鬼魂在哀怨
Like this whining growl.
谢谢你提供的情况
Thanks for your time.
因此当地警察就没再继续调查这事
So the local police have not ruled out foul play.
很显然他们已经尽力过了
Apparently, there were signs of a struggle.
他们也有可能是对的 可能是起诱拐案件
You know, they could be right. Could just be a kidnapping.
可能这也不是我们的事
Maybe this isn't our kind of gig.
可能不是的 但看看这个
Yeah, maybe not.
爸爸圈出了这个地方 迪恩
Except for this. Dad marked the area, Dean.
注明"可能在这捕杀到攻击人类的幽灵"
Possible hunting grounds of a phantom attacker.
父亲为什么这么做
Why would he even do that?
他发现当地有很多关于夜晚
Well, he found a lot of local folklore...
有黑影出没来抓人并消失的民间传说
about a dark figure that comes out at night grabs people, then vanishes
他还发现了这
He found this too
这个县失踪人口要远远高出 这个州的其他县
This county has more missing persons per capita than anywhere in the state.
- 这点很奇怪 - 是的
- That is weird. - Yeah.
那幽灵是不是通常在人熟睡时作案
Don't phantom attackers usually snatch people from their beds?
詹金是在停车场被抓走的
Jenkins was taken from a parking lot.
有很多幽灵都会抓捕人类
Well, there are all kinds. Spring Heeled Jacks, phantom gassers.
他们时时刻刻都会抓捕人类
They take people anywhere, any time.
我也不清楚这到底算不算我们的事
I don't know if this is our kind of gig either.
你说的没错 我们明天得查个究竟
Yeah, you're right. We should ask around more tomorrow.
是啊
Right.
我看见5里外有间汽车旅馆
I saw a motel about five miles back.
是吗 太好啦
Whoa, whoa, easy.
让我们去别处逛逛
Let's have another round.
我们得早点出发
We should get an early start.
你得知道怎么样去找点乐子 大婶
You really know how to have fun, don't you, Grandma?
那好吧
All right.
等下去外面找你 我得先去解决生理问题
I'll meet you outside. I gotta take a leak.
嘿 你们在这里外面呆了有一个小时了吧 能不能问下
Hey. You guys been outside around here in, like, the last hour or so?
萨姆
Sam!
Sammy?
萨姆
Sam.
我能为你做些什么么 华盛顿警官
So, what can we do for you, Officer Washington?
我在找一个失踪人口
I'm working a missing persons.
我不知道詹金的案子已经归州 警察局管了
Didn't know the Jenkins case was being covered by state police.
不是这个 我是说另外一个案子
Uh, no. No. This is someone else.
事实上那是我堂弟
Actually, it's my cousin.
我们昨晚还一起在公路边的酒吧里
We were having a few last night at this bar by the highway.
然后我就再没见到过他
I haven't seen him since.
你堂弟是不是喝醉了
Your cousin have a drinking problem?
你说萨姆吗 才喝了两瓶啤酒 他还能唱卡拉OK呢
Sam? Two beers, and he's doing karaoke.
他肯定没喝醉 他是被人带走了
He wasn't drunk. He was taken.
那好吧
All right.
他姓什么
What's his name?
温彻斯特
Winchester
萨姆·温彻斯特
Sam Winchester.
要搜索一下吗
Like the rifle?
好的
All right.
萨姆·温彻斯特
"Samuel Winchester."
他有个哥哥叫迪恩·温彻斯特 死于圣路易斯
So you know that his brother, Dean Winchester, died in St. Louis...
还是个杀人嫌疑犯
and was suspected of murder?
是叫迪恩
Yeah, Dean.
那是他们家的害群之马
Kind of the black sheep of the family.
但长得还挺英俊
Handsome, though
没在现在的监控上有看到你堂弟
He's not showing up in current reports.
我到是注意到一些
Oh, l already have a lead.
我看到那条公路上有个监视器
I saw a surveillance camera out by the highway.
- 那是县交通计算机监视器 - 没错
- County traffic cam? - Right. Yeah.
我想那东西应该能拍到 是什么带走了我堂弟
I'm thinking the camera picked up whatever took him.
或者是谁带走了他
Or whoever.
好吧 我联系下那个部门
Well, l have access to the cam footage down at the County Works Department.
与此同时 让我们按照正规手续来办
But, well, in the meantime, let's do this the right way.
你先填一下这个失踪人口表好吗
Why don't you fill out a missing persons report...
就坐那边填吧
and sit tight over here?
警官 他的家人
Officer, look, he's family.
拜托我务必看好他
I kind of look out for the kid.
所以让我帮你一起找他吧
You gotta let me go with you.
对不起 我不能这样做
I'm sorry. I can't do that.
那好 你告诉我
Well, tell me something.
在你们县的失踪者中
Your county has its fair share of missing persons.
有找回来的吗
Any of them come back?
萨姆的失踪我也有责任
Sam's my responsibility.
所以得必须找回他
And he's coming back.
我得找到他
I'm bringing him back.
格雷格 我想我找些线索了
Greg. I think we got something.
计算机监控器每3秒钟拍摄图象一次
These traffic cams take an image every three seconds.
拍摄图象一次
It's part of the Amber Alert program.
而这些图象是在你堂弟失踪的 那段时间里拍的
These images were all taken around the time your cousin disappeared.
我要的不是这些
This really isn't what I'm looking for.
等一下在下结论
Just wait. Wait. Next one.
下一张 这张就是萨姆离开酒吧时拍到的
This one was taken right after Sam left the bar.
看那东西的后面
Look at the back end of that thing.
再看看那牌照
Now look at the plates.
那牌照看上去很新 这车可能是偷来的
The plates look new. It was probably stolen.
所以那个换上新牌照的贼 肯定与你堂弟的失踪有关
So whoever's driving that rust bucket must be involved.
你听到的引擎声了吗
Hear that engine?
听到了
Yeah.
有点象鬼魂的哀怨 不是吗
Kind of a whining growl, isn't it?
是有点
Sure.
我非常讨厌这个声音
I'll be damned.
你还活着吗
You're alive?
嘿 你还好吗
Hey, you okay?
你看我还好吗
Does it look like l'm doing okay?
我们在哪里
Where are we?
我不知道
l don't know.
我想可能在乡村 有乡村的气息
The country, I think. Smells like the country.
你就是詹金吗
You're Alvin Jenkins, aren't you?
没错
Yeah.
我正在找你
Wow. l was looking for you.
是吗
Oh, yeah?
- 嗯 - 那你这次的营救看来没有成效
- Well - no offense, but this is a piss poor rescue.
但我兄弟还在外面
My brother's out there right now too.
他正在找我们 因此…
He's looking for us. So....
所以他就能找到我们是吗
So he's not gonna find us.
我们根本不知道自己在什么地方
We're in the middle of nowhere...
也不知道他们会对我们怎么样
waiting for them to come back and do God knows what to us.
它们是什么物体
What are they?
你看到过它们吗
Whatever grabbed us.
你在说些什么
What are you talking about?
它们看上去象什么
What do they look like?
管好你自己吧
See for yourself.
别抓我
Leave me alone.
别碰我 别抓我
Don't you touch me. You leave me alone!
我真笨
I'll be damned.
- 它们是人类 - 是人类
- They're just people. - Yeah.
那你以为什么
What did you expect?
他们多久才给你吃的
How often do they feed you?
一天一次
Once a day.
他们用那东西打开笼子
hey use that thing over there to open the cage.
这就是唯一你能看到他们的时候吗
And that's the only time you see them?
太远了 但我在等待
So far. But l'm waiting.
等待什么
Waiting for what?
下顿毒打
Ned Beatty time, man.
我想那是你最担心的吧
l think that's the least of your worries.
你觉得是吗
Oh, yeah?
- 是的 - 你认为他们想要什么
- Yeah. - What do you think they want, then?
那得看他们是什么人
Depends on who they are.
他们是群有精神病的农民
They're a bunch of psycho, hillbilly rednecks, you ask me.
如果你觉得不对 那你看看四周
Looking for love in all the wrong places.
下一个交通监视器离这里有50里
Okay. The next traffic cam...
但你记得事发地不在那里
is 50 miles from here and your pickup didn't pass that one.
所以他们肯定在其他地方
So.... lt must have pulled off somewhere.
在这里我没看见有路啊
I don't see any other roads here.
这里还有许多路没有开垦过
A lot of these backwoods properties have their own private roads.
那好吧
Great.
所以 格雷格
So, Gregory?
怎么了
Yeah.
我查了你的工号
I ran your badge number
当我们与州立警察合作时的惯例
It's routine when working a case with state police...
为的是了解你的身份和工作任务
for accounting purposes, and what have you.
他们反馈给我说
And, they just got back to me.
说你的工号被盗用了
Says here your badge was stolen.
还有这是你的照片
And there's a picture of you.
我减肥了
I lost some weight.
而且我得了象迈克尔·杰克逊样的皮肤病
And l got that Michael Jackson skin disease.
你下车一下好吗
Okay. Would you step out of the car, please?
听着
Look, look, look.
你如果想要逮捕我 那没问题
You want to arrest me? That's fine.
我发誓 我会合作的
I'll cooperate, l swear.
但你得先让我找到萨姆
But first, please, let me find Sam.
但我根本不知道你是谁即使萨姆失踪了
I don't even know who you are.Or if this Sam person is missing.
看着我的眼睛 你觉得我是在说慌吗
Look in my eyes and tell me I'm lying about this.
证件被偷了吗
Identity theft?
你是一个无证警官
You're impersonating an officer.
事情是这样的
Here's the thing.
当我们都年幼的时候
When we were young...
我有一次差点把他推入火坑
l pretty much pulled him from a fire.
然后从那起 我觉得我有亏欠于他
And ever since then, I've felt responsible for him.
我现在的职责就是保证他的安全
You know, like it's my job to keep him safe.
我只是担心如果不快点找到他…
I'm just afraid if we don't find him fast....
求你了
Please.
他是我的家人
He's my family.
对不起
I'm sorry.
对不起 你让我很难办
You've given me no choice.
在我们找到萨姆·温彻斯特后
I have to take you in.
我不得不逮捕你
After we find Sam Winchester.
你叫什么来着
What's your name again?
萨姆
lt's Sam.
放弃吧 萨姆 不可能逃出去的
Why don't you give it up, Sammy. There's no way out.
我不会放弃的
Don't call me Sammy.
那是什么
What is it?
支架
It's a bracket.
哦 天那 是个支架
Oh, thank God, a bracket.
我们现在能够的到了
Now we got them, huh?
太短了
Must have been a short.
可能你把一些东西敲松了
Maybe you knocked something loose.
我想你还是呆在这里好
l think you should get back in, Jenkins.
- 你说什么 - 这才是正确的
- What? - This isn't right.
你想离开这里吗
Don't you want to get out of here?
想 但是光这样不行
Yeah, but that was too easy.
我想离开这里
I'm gonna get out of here.
我离开后去找援助 好吗
Gonna send help. Don't worry.
别那样 我是认真的
No. I'm serious.
詹金 这可能是个圈套
Jenkins. This might be a trap.
再见 萨姆
Bye, Sammy.
詹金
Jenkins!
谢谢
Thank you.
那好吧 警官
Okay, officer.
听着 我并不是想得寸进尺
Look, I don't mean to press my luck.
有什么事你说吧
Your luck is so pressed.
我只是想知道
Right.
I was wondering
你为什么会帮我
why are you helping me out anyway?
为什么不直接铐了我
Why don't you just lock me up?
我兄弟三年前也失踪了
My brother Riley disappeared three years ago.
就象萨姆一样
A lot like Sam.
我们到处找他但没有结果
We searched for him, but nothing.
我了解那种感到对别人的安全 有责任的感觉
I know what it's like to feel responsible for someone, and for them....
走吧 让我们继续
Come on. Let's keep at it.
停在这里
Wait, wait, wait. Pull over here. Pull over.
从这里开始就是岔道了
This is the first turn off I've seen so far.
你呆在这里 我去看看
You stay here. I'll check it out.
不行
No way.
嘿
Hey.
你不是警察 而且还是带罪之身
You're a civilian. And a felon, I think.
这样我不能带着你继续了
I'm not taking you with me.
你去哪里都得和我一起
You're not going without me.
那好吧
All right.
你得答应我你不会擅自行动
You promise you won't get involved?
让我来处理这件事
You'll let me handle it.
好的 我答应你
Yeah. I promise.
拿着它
Shake on it.
噢 别这样
Oh, come on.
这太可笑了
This is ridiculous.
凯瑟琳 我想你是需要我的帮助的
Kathleen, l think you're gonna need my help.
我能行 谢谢你
I'll manage, thank you.
看来以后得带点回形针在身边
I gotta start carrying paperclips.
有人吗
Hello?
房子里面有人吗
Is anybody home?
嗨 你是谁
Hi. How are you?
你是谁
Who are you?
我是凯瑟琳 我是代理治安长官
I'm Kathleen, I'm a deputy.
你叫什么
What's your name?
米西
Missy.
米西 这个名字不错
Missy. That's a pretty name.
米西 你妈妈在家吗
Missy, is your mom home?
她死了
She's dead.
对不起 那你爸爸呢
I'm sorry. What about your dad?
不在
No?
我们进来看一下吗
Can l come in for a minute?
我只是想让你认一下这个照片
I just want you to look at a picture.
你有看见过这个人吗
You seen that guy?
看这照片
Look at that picture.
你说什么
What?
他好象受伤了
That's gonna hurt.
米西 小甜心
Missy, sweetheart...
告诉你哥哥我想见他
go tell your brothers I wanna see them.
是的 爸爸
Yes, Daddy.
就差一点
Son of a bitch.
我从没见过他如此震怒过
But l've never seen him so angry before.
还从没被就警察跟踪过
Well, Lee, never been followed by the police before.
你说的没错
You all right?
你是萨姆·温彻斯特吗 是你吗
Are you Sam Winchester? Aren't you?
是的
Yeah.
你的
Your....
你的堂兄在找你
Your cousings looking for you.
谢天谢地
Thank God.
他在哪里
Where is he?
我…
I....
我把他铐在我车上了
I cuffed him to my car.
萨姆
Sam?
你受伤了吗
Are you hurt?
没有
No.
见到你太好了
Damn, it's good to see you.
你怎么打开手铐的
How did you get out of the cuffs?
因为我还有点小伎俩
I know a trick or two.
好吧
All right.
从这些看上去 他们真的很残忍
These locks look like they're gonna be a bitch.
那里是自动控制门
There's some kind of automatic control right there.
你看到过他们吗
Have you seen them?
他们是人类
Yeah.Dude. They're just people.
他们打过你吗
And they jumped you?
那门看上去好象锈掉了 兄弟
Must be getting a little rusty there, kiddo.
他们想要什么
What do they want?
我不清楚
l don't know.
他们让詹金逃走了 但我想那是个圈套
They let Jenkins go, but that was some sort of trap.
但这个对我无效
It doesn't make any sense to me.
那就是我想说的
Yeah, well, that's the point.
他们和我们以前遇到的不同
You know, with our usual playmates, there's rules.
他们只是疯狂的人类
But with people, they're just crazy.
这之外有看到其他东西吗
See anything else out there?
他有很多车藏在后面
Uh, there's a dozen junked cars out back.
我想每次他们抓一个人来 顺便把他的车也一起抢过来
When they take someone, they take their car too.
你有看到过一只10岁左右的野马吗
Did you see a black Mustang? About 1 0 years old?
我有见过
Yeah, actually l did.
你兄弟的吗
Your brother's.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
这里还真是个鬼地方
Let's get you guys
我们得好好教训下他们
out and take care of those bastards.
这个需要钥匙 有钥匙吗
This thing takes a key? Key?
不清楚
l don't know.
那好吧 我会找到它的
All right. I better go find it.
嘿
Hey.
小心点
Be careful.
我会的
Yeah.
天那
Yikes.
我就说嘛
I'll say it again.
看来我找到元凶了
Demons, I get.
这里人都疯了
People are crazy.
什么
What the...?
没事的 我不会伤害你的
It's okay. I'm not gonna hurt you.
我知道
I know.
- 爸爸 - 天哪
- Daddy! - Jeez.
爸爸
Daddy!
我得先把你揍扁
I'm gonna kick your ass first.
还有你们
And then yours.
让我们把他关起来吧
Come on. Let's hunt him.
是啊 这家伙很会打架
Yeah, this one's a fighter.
看来把他关起来的乐趣还不少
Sure would be fun to hunt.
你肯定在和我开玩笑
Oh, you gotta be kidding me.
这就是你们的职业
That's what this is about. You
就是猎捕人类吗
You yahoos hunt people?
你早该死了
You ever killed before?
你说什么
What?
那得看你想干什么
Well, that depends on what you mean.
我一辈子都在猎捕
I've hunted all my life.
就像我的父亲和祖父
Just like my father, his before him.
我猎捕熊和鹿
I've hunted deer and bear.
我有次捕到了美洲狮
I even got a cougar once. Oh, boy.
但最棒的猎物是… 人类
But the best hunt is human.
没有什么比的上这个
Oh, there's nothing like it.
把他们的命掌控自己的手上…
Holding their life in your hands.
看着他们眼神中的恐惧 这让你感到活力无穷
Seeing the fear in their eyes just before they go dark.
你真变态
You're a sick puppy.
我们给他们武器
We give them a weapon.
我们给他们有反抗的机会
Give them a fighting chance.
这种猎捕人类就向一种传统
It's kind of like our tradition.
从父辈传给小辈
Passed down father to son.
当然每年就捕一到两个人
Course, only one or two a year.
从不过多来引起政府的注意
Never enough to bring the law down.
还不至于受到他们的"照顾"
We never been that sloppy.
别太低估自己
Oh. Yeah, well, don't sell yourself short.
你们引起的骚动不小
You're plenty sloppy.
因此你才和那漂亮的警察一起来 是吗
So, what, you with that pretty cop?
你也是警察吗
You a cop?
如果我告诉你
If l tell you...
你得答应我别把我 扔进那火坑
you promise not to make me into an ashtray?
我让你还呆在这里
Only reason l don't let my boys take you right here and now...
就说明我还有问题要问
is that there's something I need to know.
那好 那我就告诉你 别跟你姐姐结婚
Yeah, how about it's not nice to marry your sister?
告诉我
Tell me.
告诉我 还会有警察来找你吗
Any other cops gonna come looking for you?
那吃了我吧
Eat me.
不不不 等等 等等
No, no, no. Wait, wait, wait.
你可能真的会
You actually might.
你觉得这很有趣吗
You think this is funny?
你给我们家带来了麻烦
You brought this down on my family.
好吧
All right.
看来你想玩游戏
You wanna play games?
那我们就来玩玩
We'll play some games.
孩子们 看来我们晚上我们还有场猎要打
Looks like we're gonna have a hunt tonight, after all, boys.
你来选猎物
And you get to pick the animal.
是那个小子还是那警察
The boy or the cop.
等等
Okay, wait, wait, wait. No.
没人会来找我 只有我们三个
Look. Nobody's coming for me, all right? lt's just us.
如果你不选 那我来
You don't choose, l will.
你这个狗娘养的
You son of a bitch.
这次 我会对准眼睛
Next time, I'll take an eye.
好吧 我选那小子
All right. The guy, the guy, take the guy.
李 马上去办
Go do it.
别让他出笼子
Don't let him out, though.
直接在笼子里杀了他
Shoot him in the cage.
你说什么
What?
我记得你说过只是猎捕他而已
You were gonna hunt him.
你还会给他逃跑的机会
You were gonna give him a chance.
李 你杀了那小子之后 再杀了那婊子
Lee, when you're done with the boy, shoot the bitch too.
在警察来之前 你得把那清理干净
We gotta clean up this mess up before any more cops come running out here.
你想干什么
What are you doing?
如果你杀了我兄弟 我发誓肯定会杀了你
If you hurt my brother, I'll kill you, l swear.
我会把你们全杀了
I'll kill you all.
李
Lee!
该死的
Damn.
李
Lee!
贾里德 你和我一起去
Jared, you come with me.
米西
Missy...
你看着他
you watch him, now.
李 你在哪里
Lee? Where are you?
李
Lee.
该死的 贾里德 开灯
Damn it. Jared, get the lights.
保险丝被弄断了
They must have pulled the fuses.
你这个婊子
You stupid....
住手
Hey.
你看着他 你先走
I'll watch this one. You go ahead.
快走
Go ahead.
你伤了我的家人
You hurt my family
我要杀了你 臭婊子
I'm gonna bleed you, bitch.
你杀了我兄弟
You killed my brother.
你兄弟
Your brother.
我明白了
Now I see.
告诉我为什么
Just tell me why.
因为很有趣
Because it's fun.
那女孩在哪里
Where's the girl?
被锁在壁橱里
Locked in the closet.
那她爸爸怎么样了
What about the dad?
我杀了他 快逃吧
Shot. Trying to escape.
我想车在警察局那
l think the car's at the police station.
呼叫后援
backup units en route to your location.
所以
So...
州警察局和FBI的人一个小时就会到这里
state police and the FBI are gonna be here within the hour.
他们想要和你谈谈
They're gonna wanna talk to you.
我建议你们最好和他们说明下情况
I suggest that you're both long gone by then.
谢谢
Thanks.
我并不想冒犯你
I don't mean to press our luck
但我们不能在这里久留
but we're in the middle of nowhere.
我们到哪里可以搭顺风车
Think we could catch a ride?
从这一直走
Start walking.
如果看见巡逻车的话就可以
Duck if you see a squad car.
听起来不错 谢谢
Sound great to me. Thanks.
我对你兄弟的事很遗憾
Listen sorry about your brother.
谢谢
Thank you.
当知道他发生了什么事 真的很难过
It was really hard not knowing what happened.
我想当我知道事实的时候 会轻松一点
I thought it would be easier once I knew the truth.
但… 并不是那么容易接受得了
But.... lt isn't, really.
不管怎么样 你们可以走了
Anyway, you should go.
但别在干那事了
Don't ever do that again.
做什么
Do what?
像你那样失踪
Go missing like that.
你在担心我吗
You were worried about me.
要是你再象这样失踪 我也不会再来找你
All I'm saying is, you vanish like that again, l'm not looking for you.
你还是会的
Sure you won't
我不会
l'm not.
所以你才会被那13岁女孩看着 是吧
So you got sidelined by a thirteen year olds girl?
闭嘴
Shut up.
闭嘴 只是开开玩笑 你那里是不是生锈了 兄弟
Just saying, you're getting rusty, kiddo.
你闭嘴
Shut up.